Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 197990; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Life: 1936: July: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198546 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1936: August, 198545 (Offsite-box 431-432)
  - Life: 1936: September: Misc, 198544 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1936: September: Dummy #2 (Rehearsal), 198543 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1936: October: Ingersoll's Opus, 198542 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1936: October: Misc, 198541 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1936: November: Outside Comment, 198540 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1936: December: Outside Comment, 198539 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1936: December: Misc, 198538 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1936: November: Misc, 198537 (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1936: November: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198536 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1937: "Coming to Life", 198535 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 10-11)
  - Life: 1937: Edit, 198534 (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1937: Edit [RESTRICTED], 198533 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: Jan.-June, 198532 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: July-Dec., 198531 (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: July-Dec. [RESTRICTED], 198530 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: RCA "Listen" Campaign, 198529 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: "Birth of a Baby", 198528 (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: "Birth of a Baby" [RESTRICTED], 198527 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: Housing Series, 198526 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: Misc, 198525 (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED], 198524 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1938: Publishing: CSMA #1, 198523 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 23-24)
  - Life: 1938: Publishing, 198522 (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1938: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 198521 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Commissioned Art Series, 198520 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Housing Series, 198519 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198518 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1939: Publishing, 198517 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Contemplated editorial on aid to allies by HRL, never run, 198516 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1940: Edit: Housing Series, 198515 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1940: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198514 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1940: Publishing, 198513 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1941 &Before: Edit: Corcoran Lawsuit, 198512 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1941 &Before: Edit: Corcoran Lawsuit [RESTRICTED], 198511 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198510 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 10)
  - Life: Publishing, 198509 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, History of Picture Magazines, 198508 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1942 &Before: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Depositions, 198507 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 13)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (1), 198506 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (1) [RESTRICTED], 198505 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (2), 198504 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (2) [RESTRICTED], 198503 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198502 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198501 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: "Open Letter" to England, 10/17/42, 198500 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool, 198499 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool [RESTRICTED], 198498 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Publishing, 198497 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1943: Edit, 198496 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1943: Edit [RESTRICTED], 198495 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1943: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool, 198494 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1943: Publishing, 198493 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: "Dear Gang" Letters (to Photographers), 198492 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1944: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool, 198491 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1944: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198490 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1944: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198489 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1944: Publishing, 198488 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198487 (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198486 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool, 198485 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 30)
  - Life: 1945: Publishing, 198484 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 31)
  - Life: 1946: Anniversary 10th, 198483 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 32-33)
  - Life: 1946: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198482 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 1-2)
  - Life: 1946: Publishing, 198481 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1947: Edit: Art, 198480 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1947: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198479 (Offsite-box 434)
  - Life: 1947: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198478 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1947: Publishing, 198477 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1948: Circulation Budgets, 198476 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Art, 198475 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1948: Edit: Art &Round Table on Art, 198474 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1948: Edit: Organization, 198473 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1948: Publishing, 198472 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1948: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198471 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 12)
  - Life: Edit: Roundtable, "Pursuit of Happiness", 198470 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 13)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Department Story Seg. to E.K.T., 198469 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198468 (Offsite-box 434)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198467 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Round Tables on Housing &Movies, 198466 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1949: Publishing, 198465 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 19-20)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: 3/27 Vatican Grottos, 198464 (Offsite-box 434)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: 3/27 Vatican Grottos [RESTRICTED], 198463 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: Comment, 198462 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1950: Publishing, 198461 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198460 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 24)
  - Life:1951: Edit: Comment, 198459 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1951: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198458 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1951: Publishing, 198457 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1952: Edit: Comment, 198456 (Offsite-box 434, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1952: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198455 (Offsite-box 434-435)
  - Life: 1952: Publishing, 198454 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 2)
  - Life: Edit: Art, 198453 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1953: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198452 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 4-5)
  - Life: 1953: Edit: Comment, 198451 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1953: Publishing, 198450 (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1953: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 198449 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Comment, 198448 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: German Issue, 198447 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: HRL's Marked Copies, 198446 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June, 198445 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-August, 198444 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Sept., 198443 (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Sept. [RESTRICTED], 198442 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Oct.-Nov., 198441 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Dec., 198440 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1954: Publishing, 198439 (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1954: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 198438 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Comment, 198437 (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Comment [RESTRICTED], 198436 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April, 198435 (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April [RESTRICTED], 198434 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous: May-Dec., 198433 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Religion Series, 198432 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1955: Publishing, 198431 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Comment, 198430 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Hungary [empty], 198429 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Russian Revolution, 198428 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Segregation Series, 198427 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June, 198426 (Offsite-box 435, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-Dec., 198425 (Offsite-box 435-436)
  - Life: 1956: Publishing, 198424 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1957: Edit: Comment, 198423 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1957: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198422 (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1957: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198421 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1957: Publishing, 198420 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March, 198419 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 7-8)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Miscellaneous: April-Dec., 198418 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Comment, 198417 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Education Series, 198416 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Russian Revolution Series, 198415 (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Russian Revolution Series [RESTRICTED], 198414 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1958: Publishing, 198413 (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1958: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 198412 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Astronauts, 198411 (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 198410 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Comment, 198409 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April, 198408 (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April [RESTRICTED], 198407 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous: May-Dec., 198406 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 20-21)
  - Life: 1959: Publishing, 198405 (Offsite-box 436, Folder 22-23)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Astronauts, 198404 (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], 198403 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Comment, 198402 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June, 198401 (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June [RESTRICTED], 198400 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-Sept., 198399 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: Oct.-Dec., 198398 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 5-6)
  - Life: Edit: National Purpose: Letters Department Report, 198397 (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: Edit: National Purpose: Letters Department Report [RESTRICTED], 198396 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1960: Publishing, 198395 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 8-9)
  - Life: 1960 &Later: Edit: National Purpose Series: Miscellaneous, 198394 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 10-11)
  - Life: 1960 &Later: Edit: National Purpose Series: Contributions, A-Z, 198393 (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: 1960 &Later: Edit: National Purpose Series: Contributions, A-Z [RESTRICTED], 198392 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life: 1936-1959: Adv. Promotion: Advertisers, 198391 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 13)
  - Life Circulation Company [empty], 198390 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 15)
  - Life International: Circulation Mailings, 198389 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 16)
  - Life International: 1940-1944, 198388 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 17)
  - Life International: 1945: Proposal, 198387 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 18)
  - Life International: 1945: Miscellaneous, 198386 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 19)
  - Life International: 1946, 198385 (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life International: 1946 [RESTRICTED], 198384 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Life International: 1947-1950, 198383 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 1-2)
  - Life International: 1951-1955, 198382 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 3)
  - Life International: 1956, 198381 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 4-5)
  - Life International: 1957, 198380 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 6)
  - Life International: 1958, 198379 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 7)
  - Life International: 1959, 198378 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 8)
  - Life International: 1960, 198377 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 9)
  - Life Spanish: 1942-1952, 198376 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 10-11)
  - Life Spanish: 1953-1955, 198375 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 12)
  - Life Spanish: 1956-1958, 198374 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 13)
  - Life Spanish: 1959-1960, 198373 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 14)
  - Literary Digest, 198372 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 15)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1933: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198371 (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1933: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198370 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: November, 198369 (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: November [RESTRICTED], 198368 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1935: Movie: March of the Years, 198367 (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1935: Movie: March of the Years [RESTRICTED], 198366 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Dec., 198365 (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Dec. [RESTRICTED], 198364 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Jan-July, 198363 (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Jan-July [RESTRICTED], 198362 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: August, 198361 (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: August [RESTRICTED], 198360 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: September, 198359 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 23)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: October, 198358 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 24)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Prospectus: August, 198357 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 25)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March, 198356 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 1-2)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: April-June, 198355 (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: April-June [RESTRICTED], 198354 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: July-Dec., 198353 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 4)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Pre-Release: Experimental Scripts, 198352 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 5)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1936: Movie: "Four Hours a Year", 198351 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 6)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1936: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198350 (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1936: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198349 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1937: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198348 (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1937: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198347 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1938: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198346 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 9)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1939: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198345 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 10)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1940: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198344 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 11)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1941: Movie: U.S. Senate Investigation, 198343 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 12)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1941: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198342 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 13)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1942: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198341 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 14)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1943: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198340 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 15)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1944: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198339 (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1944: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198338 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1945: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198337 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 17)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1946: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198336 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 18)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1947: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198335 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 19)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1948: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198334 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 20)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1949: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198333 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 21)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1950: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198332 (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1950: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198331 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1951 & Later: Movie: Miscellaneous, 198330 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 23)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Movie: Miscellaneous: Undated, 198329 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 24)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Copyrights, 198328 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 25)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Music, 198327 (Offsite-box 439, Folder 26)
    Scope and Contents Note
    Includes audiovisual materials.
    2 audiotape reels: analog; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Labels: "Return to: Time Inc. Archives. 22-58. Not for commercial use".
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Rating, 198326 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 1)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1932: Radio, 198325 (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1932: Radio [RESTRICTED], 198324 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1933: Radio, 198323 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1938: Radio, 198322 (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1938: Radio [RESTRICTED], 198321 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1939-1941: Radio, 198320 (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1939-1941: Radio [RESTRICTED], 198319 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1942-1956: Radio, 198318 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 7-8)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Promotion (Samples), 198317 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 9-10)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Special Shows, 198316 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 11)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1937-1948: Television, 198315 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 12)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1949-1950: Television, 198314 (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1949-1950: Television [RESTRICTED], 198313 (Offsite-box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1951-1960: Television, 198312 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 15)
  - Newsbureau & News Services (AP & UP) [empty], 198311 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 16)
  - Offices: Chicago, 198310 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 17)
  - Offices: Cleveland: 1925-1928, 198309 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 18)
  - Offices: New York: 1937 & Before, 198308 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 20)
  - Offices: New York: 1937 & Before: T&L Building, 9 Rockefeller Plaza (Pre-Move), 198307 (Offsite-box 440)
  - Offices: New York: 1937 & Before: T&L Building, 9 Rockefeller Plaza (Pre-Move) [RESTRICTED], 198306 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Offices: New York: 1944: Empire State Building, 198305 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 23)
  - Offices: New York: 1944-1948: Proposed New Sites (Marguery), 198304 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 24)
  - Offices: New York: 1938-1960: T&L Building, 9 Rockefeller Plaza, 198303 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 25-26)
  - Offices: New York: 1949-1955: Proposed New Sites (Incl. Non-NYC: Rye & Philly-Wil), 198302 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 1-2)
  - Offices: New York: 1955: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move), 198301 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Offices: New York: 1955: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) [RESTRICTED], 198300 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Offices: New York: 1956: T&L Bldg, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move), 198299 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 4)
  - Offices: New York: 1957: T&L Bldg, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move), 198298 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 5)
  - Offices: New York: 1958: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move), 198297 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Offices: New York: 1958: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) {RESTRICTED], 198296 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Offices: New York: 1959: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move), 198295 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 7)
  - Offices: New York: 1960: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Move), 198294 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 8)
  - Offices: Miscellaneous, 198293 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 9)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1926-1932, 198292 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 19)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1933-1935, 198291 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: Jan.-Feb., 198290 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 11)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: Mar.-June, 198289 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 12)
  - Personnel & Organization: Communism:"High Time": 1939, 198288 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 13)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: July-Dec., 198287 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: July-Dec. [RESTRICTED], 198286 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Matusow, Harvey: 1952-1953, 198285 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 15)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities, 198284 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 16)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1939-1946, 198283 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 17)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1947, 198282 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 18)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1948-1960, 198281 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 19)
  - Personnel & Organization: Senior Group Trust: 1939-1949, 198280 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Senior Group Trust: 1939-1949 [RESTRICTED], 198279 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1936, 198278 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 21)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1937: Jan.-July, 198277 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1937: Jan.-July [RESTRICTED], 198276 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1937: Aug.-Dec., 198275 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 23)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: Sept.-Dec., 198274 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: Sept.-Dec. [RESTRICTED], 198273 (Offsite-box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: Jan.-April, 198272 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 25)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: May-Aug., 198271 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 26)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1940, 198270 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 27-28)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1941, 198269 (Offsite-box 441-442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1941 [RESTRICTED], 198268 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1942, 198267 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1942 [RESTRICTED], 198266 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1943-1944, 198265 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1943-1944 [RESTRICTED], 198264 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Talent Hunt: 1945, 198263 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 6)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1945, 198262 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1945 [RESTRICTED], 198261 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1946, 198260 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 8-9)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1947-1948, 198259 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1949-1950, 198258 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 11-12)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1951-1956, 198257 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1951-1956 [RESTRICTED], 198256 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1957-1960, 198255 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 15-16)
  - Production: Corporate: 1938-1941, 198254 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 17)
  - Production: Corporate: 1942-1945, 198253 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Production: Corporate: 1942-1945 [RESTRICTED], 198252 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Production: Corporate: 1946-1948, 198251 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 19)